I welcome everyone to our YouTube
channel center friends, today I am going to tell you
ICICI Lombard name board and
what to do in it, you have to
register fully, okay so you have to
click on install on it, it will take you directly
and here you will get an option and it will
take you directly to the play store, so this is it
and here is Tal Care Insurance,
okay now I have to click on install it
friends and this install
hello friends Nilesh has been installed, now
we open it friends and it is done,
now you have to keep clicking next and
click on continue,
after clicking on continue, such an option will
come to you, so you have to
enter the mobile number here,
okay, I will put it here,
now you have to enter the first name here,
I will put it here, Namaskar
and enter the date of birth here, so
friends,
you have to quickly enter everything here,
whatever you will ask for,
okay, okay, do
not enter all these things, you have to click on ok, to
enter this fair,
I will put it here  But I will put it on the email ID,
okay, it is done
and now we have to
click on accept the function here and
also click on WhatsApp and
click on process, please wait reading and OTP,
OTP is going to come to us, just
click on it and automatically
you will get the OTP here, okay, so now we have
come in front of us, now we have to do this,
health insurance, motor insurance, travel
insurance, home insurance, so we do
helping here and here the company has
entered the Employee ID, I miss you,
you just have to decide this, okay
and click on it, but it will be done
for you,
so our registration
is already done here, this is all we have to do, we do
n't have to do anything else, okay, so
thank you friends, in this way we have to
register in ICICI Lombard, I have given
you information about it,
friends, and if any problem occurs
in our comment box,
friends, you can